You really pissed me off, kid.
Stay away from my daughter.
Or I'll destroy you.
Gu Ting is the apple of your eye.
I can tell.
You'd even give your life for her.
Tell me.
What's it take to leave my daughter alone?
Let me join you.
There are so many other ways.
Why do you have to keep bothering me?
Because only you can help me.
Who the hell are you?
What are you after?
I've done my research.
You have boundaries and a conscience.
And I'm a top-tier programmer.
You scammers will definitely need me.
If you don't help me,
I'll send your fraud records to Gu Ting.
Don't you dare!
I'll kill you!
No, you won't.
If you kill me,
Gu Ting will never forgive you.
Think this through.
It's a crime.
And they'll check your background closely.
Those guys are cautious.
Don't worry about that.
Just introduce me to them.
Fine, I'll do it.
What about my daughter?
I promise I'll talk her into going home.
So I'm supposed to thank you now?
Don't mention it.
Just helping each other out.
Uncle.
The cash flow has dropped so much lately.
You better give me a good explanation.
Boss, the cops are cracking down lately.
What did you call me?
I'm sorry, Sir.
Hurry up and find me a capable programmer.
We have a big deal coming up.
Do this right to make up for the losses.
Understood.
Keep a close eye on Grass Snake for me.
You're really willing to send me away?
Of course not.
Then...
After this is done,
you'll get everything you deserve.
And...
your freedom.
Bro Snake,
those programmers...
screwed up again.
What good are you?!
Get out of here!
You're a bunch of useless trash!
Get the hell out!
Yeah?
Bro Snake,
didn't you ask me to find you some help?
I found someone suitable.
And he's a senior programmer.
How's his background?
I did a preliminary check.
Should be no problem.
The main thing is,
this kid really wants to make money.
Things have been tough lately.
Several big deals got intercepted.
I'll personally screen him in a few days.
Tell him to get ready.
Will do.
Is this girl really staying out all night?
I'll teach you a lesson when you get back.
Oh, sweetie!
You're finally back.
I was just calling you.
We're so in sync!
I'm staying here for a while,
then I'm moving out.
Wait, moving out? Where will you live?
None of your business.
I should've been independent long ago.
What am I going to do if you leave?
I'll be an empty nester.
Find yourself a partner if you're lonely.
If I find a partner, what about you?
What did you say to my daughter this time?
She was crying and screaming to run away.
Can you calm down?
I tried talking to her that day.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have come home.
You'd better be telling the truth.
I'm not you.
I'm not a liar.
Come here.
Bro Snake wants to see you.
This Bro Snake has a lot of nicknames.
We all call him Grass Snake.
The guy is extremely arrogant.
Watch what you say to his face.
Alright.
I got it.
Did you prepare the story I asked you to?
Pretty much.
Whether you pass depends on your luck.
I lost 500,000 today.
Earn that 500,000 back for me.
Set up a virtual account.
Memorize this.
Get to work.
Now transfer your entire account balance,
and these funds to our official account.
You're pretty good, kid.
Police!
Stop!
Don't move!
Hands up!
I treated you like a brother.
Why would you commit crimes?
Speak!
Do it!
Enough.
Cut the act.
No one's here.
How does it feel?
You tell me.
By the way,
how is Ms. Lin doing?
The police were monitoring the situation.
Her funds are safe.
But she suffered a huge shock,
and attempted suicide.
Our people arrived in time and stopped her.
Ms. Lin!
Ms. Lin, don't do anything rash!
Ms. Lin, your money can be recovered!
Please don't take your own life!
Attempting suicide...
These scammers are truly despicable.
Ms. Lin is disabled.
It wasn't easy for her to save that money.
That was meant for her father's surgery.
Thank goodness she's okay.
Your actions were too reckless this time.
If anything had gone wrong,
the consequences would be unimaginable.
I know.
I'm glad you know.
I'm curious,
how you got an old fox like Gu Yan
to follow your orders.
Well...
I'll keep that a secret for now.
You need to know your limits.
We only control the visible operations.
There must be a mastermind behind this.
Give me your phone.
What for?
Hand it over.
I downloaded an app for you.
So you can track my location anytime.
Let me tell you,
this is an illegal invasion of privacy.
I'm not using it commercially.
Aren't you worried about my safety?
Fair enough.
For your safety,
you'll have to bear a little pain.
What do you mean?
Go on in.
Welcome back.
Bro Snake. Bro Six.
This is our new location.
Not bad.
Bringing in over 500K on your first try.
If Six hadn't been so greedy this time,
you'd be the top earner in the company.
Bro Snake, I was just thinking...
Shut up!
I know exactly what you're thinking.
You got lucky this time.
You won't be so lucky next time.
Understood.
The cops busted several small platforms.
I'm leaving the new platform setup to you.
Time is tight.
The task is heavy.
Do a good job.
Bro Snake,
do we have a big deal coming up?
Ask less,
work more.
Work hard, and you'll get your fair share.
Got it, Bro Snake.
I'll definitely work hard.
You...
don't think I don't know
you and the old man were behind this.
Just you wait.
I'll be sure to take good care of you.
Thanks for looking out for me, Bro Six.
I finally got in.
Next,
I need to find the past scam lists first.
Yaoyao.
I'll find the one who did this to you.
Why hasn't he contacted me yet?
Even though I explained I made that up,
his reaction was way too indifferent.
Is he really not into me at all?
I finally rented the place.
Move.
Behave yourself out there.
Someone will pick you up when it's time.
Got it.
Who are you?
What are you doing in our house?
Hi, I'm the tenant here.
I'm here to sign the lease.
I'm the landlord.
But we didn't rent the place to you.
How is that possible?
No, I really did rent this place.
But you didn't pay me the rent.
Hey, Li Wen.
I got scammed.